<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on Przemek Malirz</title><link>https://przemek.malirz.pl/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on Przemek Malirz</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>pl</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://przemek.malirz.pl/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pierwszy naleśnik 🥞</title><link>https://przemek.malirz.pl/blog/hugo-tailwind-githubpages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://przemek.malirz.pl/blog/hugo-tailwind-githubpages/</guid><description>To startowy wpis a jak wiadomo, pierwszy wpis jest jak pierwszy naleśnik. Ponoć takich pierwszych naleśników w blogowaniu jest po pachy. Zatem owe pierwsze moje naleśniki zamierzam zmarnować na mniej istotne tematy. Rozgrzeję się i zobaczę, jak działa to całe modne blogowanie. Obiecuję sobie, że będzie jak najkrócej. Przy okazji przetestujemy działanie Hugo i tworzenie treści za pomocą plików Markdown. Co działa a co mniej.
Będzie to post o technologiach użytych do utworzenia strony przemek.</description></item><item><title>Unlocking the Power of InnerSource: Key Strategies You Can't Ignore</title><link>https://przemek.malirz.pl/blog/innersource-essential-ways/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://przemek.malirz.pl/blog/innersource-essential-ways/</guid><description>I know that I should start with the definition of InnerSource. However, I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist to give you some concrete material to read earlier.
If you, like me, have been searching for ways to enhance collaboration among teams within your organization, or if you&amp;rsquo;re a CxO seeking to cultivate your company&amp;rsquo;s culture, elevate the quality of your products, and simultaneously reduce costs, then you should read this blog post.</description></item></channel></rss>