<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on Przemek Malirz</title><link>https://przemek.malirz.pl/en/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on Przemek Malirz</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>pl</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://przemek.malirz.pl/en/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Non-relational Oracle</title><link>https://przemek.malirz.pl/en/blog/soda-json-nosql-rdbms-oracle/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://przemek.malirz.pl/en/blog/soda-json-nosql-rdbms-oracle/</guid><description>JSON in Oracle I am sure this may seem like an obvious feature for some of you, especially those who have worked with schema-less stores. However, it is often overlooked by programmers who choose or stick with RDBMS stores. This is the audience I would like to dedicate this short write-up to.
Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong. I have nothing against relational databases. In fact, I have been working with them (particularly with Oracle) since I can remember, and this post only promotes them more.</description></item><item><title>Unlocking the Power of InnerSource: Key Strategies You Can't Ignore</title><link>https://przemek.malirz.pl/en/blog/unlocking-the-power-of-inner-source/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://przemek.malirz.pl/en/blog/unlocking-the-power-of-inner-source/</guid><description>I know that I should start with the definition of InnerSource. However, I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist to give you some concrete material to read earlier.
If you, like me, have been searching for ways to enhance collaboration among teams within your organization, or if you&amp;rsquo;re a CxO seeking to cultivate your company&amp;rsquo;s culture, elevate the quality of your products, and simultaneously reduce costs, then you should read this blog post.</description></item></channel></rss>